And then I got a D in economics. I came
home that day and I threw my books over
my head. I'm a pretty big guy. It hit
the window. The window went wobble
wobble wobble wobbled. Big big you know
14 by 20 window. My father says, "What's
the matter with you?" I said, "I just
got a D in economics." He says, "That's
it. You're getting a job working on Wall
Street." So the next day I went down and
I go to Peter Kellogg's office and
I walk in off the elevator. I get off
the elevator and I say, "Hi, I'm Steven
Kallajian. I'm here to see Mr. Kellogg."
And she says, "Follow me." I walk in
this gigantic I've never seen a room
this big in my life. And at the end of
the room was a man sitting at a desk and
he said,
Marge [snorts] says,
"Mr. Kellogg, this [clears throat] is
Steven Kallajian." He says, "Who?" I
said, "I'm Jack Kallajian's son.
I was told to meet you." So he goes,
"Marge, get him a badge." And that was
it.
He says, "You know what Stevie, you
deserve it." He wrote me a big check for
about 900 grand.
And I said, "Joe, can I ask you one more
favor?" He goes, "Really? One more
favor?" I says, "Yeah." I said, "What is
it?" I said, "Can I take the chair I was
sitting in?"
So I carried the chair to the elevator
all the way down and it was just really
just an amazing It's amazing guy. And
then I started trading my own money and
I just got into a groove.
Some days I was trading a million, some
days up to 5 million shares in a day.
And I just [clears throat] was like I
was doing high frequency trading before
high frequency trading came
came out. My My clearing firm told me I
was the number one day trader in in the
world at a 97.4%
hit ratio. You were essentially a market
maker, were you, with the volume you
were I was I mean I traded 90 to 100
names. I would have at any given time
anywhere between 30 to 50 positions. And
I'm talking positions.
Markets, speculation, [music]
and risk. This is the Chat with Traders
podcast.
>> [music]
>> All right traders, welcome to another
episode of Chat with Traders. Today's
guest is a trader who has spent more
than four decades in the markets,
starting his career on the floor of the
American Stock Exchange in 1983 and
going on to trade across equities,
futures, options, and currencies at the
highest level. But what makes his story
unique is trading wasn't just something
he discovered, it was something he grew
up around. His father, Jack Kallajian,
worked on the American Stock Exchange,
giving him a front row seat to the
markets at an early age. Watching his
father operate in that environment
helped shape not just his understanding
of trading, but his mindset, discipline,
and approach to risk. From early on, he
wasn't just interested in trading, he
was obsessed with the idea of building
technology that could see into the
future to better understand price
action, timing, and opportunity. Over
the course of his career, he's traded
nearly 2 billion shares. He's advised
hedge funds, he's built an amazing
reputation for having just a rare level
of conviction market views. And what
really sets him apart is his belief that
markets can be timed. I mean, something
most traders are told is impossible, but
he's spent decades developing systems
and proprietary tools designed to do
exactly that. His journey didn't start
with success though. Early on, he blew
through entire savings on a single
options trade, an experience that shaped
his philosophy around discipline, risk
management, and consistency. Today, he's
not just a trader, but an educator, an
entrepreneur, mentoring traders around
the world and sharing his approach to
identifying high probability setups in
real time. His style is intense,
structured, and deeply rooted in
technical analysis, focused on mastering
timing, execution, and consistency at
the highest level. So today we're going
to dive into the full journey, from
growing up around the markets to
learning hard lessons early on to
building systems designed to anticipate
price and what really it takes to
perform at a really high level for
decades. So traders, please welcome
Steven Kallajian. Welcome Steven to Chat
with Traders. How are you? That was Oh,
I got goosebumps. I'm so happy to be
here. How are you? Really? Hey Kevin,
thank you so much. And incredible. I
mean, so you've
43 years now, is that correct? August
1st, 19
83 will be 44 years
come this August 1st.
And you're just as passionate now as
ever, is that correct? I'm more
passionate now than I ever did in my
life.
Yeah, no, I'm I've been really blessed.
You know, for me
um
you know, growing up I had a desire to
play the game of baseball. Um
I actually [clears throat] went to a Met
tryout.
And
back then they did tryouts and I
actually got picked.
Guy says to me, "Well, you got to make a
decision to make. If you want to play
baseball, you can't go to college." I
said, "College? I got Well, I can say
that I got one more year of high school.
What are you talking about?" He goes,
"Oh, give me that You can't do you got
to
um you can't We can't talk to you until
you you you you graduate. So um I had a
really big passion for baseball, but
it's funny because um
in my journey later on, I noticed how
the five important rules I had for the
game of baseball really just echoed into
the game of trading, which is
consistency, discipline, confidence,
patience, and passion.
And And that's what I teach all day
long, but
I mean I teach all new traders that when
at the gate, but
and then you know, I wanted to become a
surgeon.
I really wanted to
That was another passion of mine. And
then my father once said to me,
"You know, why don't you come and come
to work with me one day?" I was 16 years
old and um
I go down you know, with him down to the
American Stock Exchange and
you know, I when I was Finally he got on
and then I went to get something to eat.
When he said, "Okay, 9:00, come right
here." And then
>> [clears throat]
>> I went to the glass doors. I went
through the glass doors
and I said, "Yes, may I have to see my
father, Jack Kallajian." He says, "Jack
Kallajian? Jack Kallajian, sign her
door." And all of a sudden I see my
father standing at the top and then
there were these beautiful granite
stairs
and I Guy gave me a badge and I went up
and as I inched up closer and closer to
him as each step that I took, I heard
the roar of the floor
of the [clears throat] floor.
And then
and then markets open at 9:30 and I hear
Oct Nov Dec. There was an Intel crowd. I
said, "Dad, what's Oct Nov Dec?" He
said, "October, November, December
are the months of the options." So
[clears throat] I just thought that you
know, it was something that my God,
every single day is a different day.
Damn. You know, I love this. And the
guys were running around and
back then the American Stock Exchange
was all options and some some stocks.
And then on the big board on the New
York Stock Exchange was all stocks and
you know, I I have to tell you it's been
a journey and a half um meeting
[clears throat] some of the best people
in the world, the some of the biggest
traders in the world, um having
relationships um
with with people that you know, you just
pinch yourself and say, "Wow, I you
know, we're you know, people I've known
for over 30, 40 years." Um it's just a
remarkable
uh
business and
>> was it what was it like at that young
age just seeing your father, Jack
Kallajian? He worked on that exchange
from 16.
You jumped you dived right in. I mean,
did you know this was what you wanted to
do
>> No. from then on? No, because I came
home one day
from after high school I went to a prep
school to play football.
I was captain of the team. We
We played all Division 1 uh
JV teams. So like for example, against
Penn State, you know, we lost a game,
but I I sacked Todd Blackledge
four times in the game. And the guy who
does the
college football games. And we played
all the big school
I decided um you know, to shift and
which was probably a mistake, but I
don't have no regrets. And then I would
I hurt my lower back when I went to uh
University of Maine and
I got recruited by some big schools, but
I said, "You know, I want to play." But
then I went to University of Maine. I
hurt my lower back really bad and I came
home to go to a community college until
I decided what I want to do. And then I
got a D in economics.
I came home that day
and I threw my books over my head. I'm a
pretty big guy. Threw my books over my
head. It hit the window. The window went
wobble wobble wobble wobbled. Big big
big big you know, 14 by 20 window. My
father says, "What's the matter with
you?" I said, "I just got a D in
economics." He says, "That's it. You're
getting a job working on Wall Street."
So the next day I went down
and um
I go to Peter Kellogg's office
I walk in off the elevator. I get off
the elevator and I say, "Hi, I'm Steven
Kallajian. I'm here to see Mr. Kellogg."
And [snorts] she says, "Follow me." I
walk in this gigantic I've never seen a
room this big in my life. And at the end
of the room was a man sitting at a desk
and he said, Marge [snorts] says,
"Mr. Kellogg, this [clears throat] is
Steven Kallajian." He says, "Who?" I
said, "I'm Jack Kallajian's son.
I was told to meet you." So he goes,
"Marge, get him a badge." And that was
it. And I got a badge working on the
floor of the American Stock Exchange and
I didn't [snorts] know if I liked it or
not, but
then I opened up a brokerage account. I
put $3,000 of my money in the account.
Back then, remember, minimum wage was
$2.10 an hour. Right? So, $2.10. So, I
was cutting lawns and doing whatever.
And then, I don't know, there was an a
stock right behind me called American
Can.
So, I picked up the phone and I said,
"Tommy, buy me five
50 calls at two and three quarters." He
goes, "Done." Right? So, I don't know
what the hell I was
I don't know what Sorry, I don't know
what the hell I was doing. And then,
next thing I know,
that was October, and then I bought more
at a dollar seven bucks seven eights. I
bought more at a dollar and a quarter, I
think. I did more at three quarters of a
dollar. And then, like
right before Well, Thanksgiving, they
were probably like at a buck and a
quarter buck and [clears throat] buck a
dollar.
>> [gasps]
>> And then, right before Christmas, they
were trading like an eighth of a dollar.
The stock had dropped like, you know,
from 51 52 down to 42. So,
I was just
put my hands
uh in my, you know, my had my head down
and my my hands on my cheek and somebody
passed me on the back. It was a Friday
right before Christmas and the guy says
to me, "Kid, go home and enjoy your
Christmas. You can't turn the machines
back on."
I'm like, "I'm flat broke. I've no money
for Christmas presents or anything."
>> [snorts]
>> And then, January rolled around and a
week before expiration,
>> [snorts]
>> the stock went from 41, and on that up
to 52, 53, 54.
So, I pick up the phone at 3:45. I said,
"Tommy, sell I don't know, 18 50 calls.
Just get me out, you know."
And I made all my money back and then
some.
And so, I trust him hanging up the
phone. My father turns to me and said,
"Are you out?" I said, "I just called
Tommy to sell. Yeah, I'm I'm going to be
out." And there's there's the broker
going in with my my order now. I can see
him.
And he said, um
"When I walked on the floor of the
American Stock Exchange on Monday, my
father said, 'I found the penny face
up.'"
And I made a wish, you know, that you
wouldn't lose any money.
He said, "What you learn from this?" I
said, "I guess whenever you have a
losing trade, you look for a penny face
up."
And he face up. And he says, "No, you
never average down, you idiot, like
that."
And as he walked away, I picked up the
phone and said, "Tommy, buy me five
Merrill calls." So, I don't know. I was
just being crazy and I learned, you
know, about consistency. I learned about
risk management. I learned a lot on my
first trade I ever did. Doesn't your
portfolio deserve the best? Then, join
tastytrade, Investopedia's best platform
for options trading 2026. Trade smarter
with advanced charting tools,
backtesting, a pre-built strategy
selector, and more features. Join
tastytrade today and earn a double
commission rebate up to $3,000 total on
your stock and ETF option trades for 30
days. Visit tastytrade.com/chat
for more info. All applicable
regulatory, exchange, and clearing fees
still apply. Options involve risk and
are not suitable for all investors.
Learn more about tastytrade promo terms
and conditions at tastytrade.com/double.
Offer expires May 31st, 2026. tastytrade
Incorporated is a registered
broker-dealer and member of FINRA, NFA,
and SIPC.
>> But then, um you know, the good Lord
gave me a gift, you know, and uh
I left uh the floor. I went to the big
board, where I became a member.
I was there during the crash of '87 and,
you know, that was pretty wild that
Friday and then that Monday. And then, I
after a couple of years there,
I went to the COMEX,
thinking about going into the gold pit.
Then, I went to the Chicago Board of
Trade to try to go into the 30-year bond
pit.
And that was a little rough because I
couldn't really get the traction of
getting the right person. They wanted me
to start at the night bonds and they
were not moving much.
But I loved the 30-year bond pit because
it was completely insane. Um and then,
I decided, you know, to come back to New
York
and I stared at the phone
and I said, "This is my last phone call
or I'm going to go to South Carolina and
become a caddy." And then,
I picked up the phone and the guy says,
"Joe wants to see you. Come tomorrow."
So, it was a guy named Joe Santana and
he had
a big floor operation.
And uh my friend Sal was upstairs
trading his money in a
beautiful condo overlooking the Battery
Park City overlooking the Statue of
Liberty.
So, Joe and I meet Joe and he says,
"Well, when can you start?"
And I said, "How about today?"
And he said, "Go ahead. Let's go. You
got X amount of dollars, go trade."
And then, um I was up about $350 on my
first trade in a stock called Compaq
Computer.
And I gave it to the broker to get me
out of the trade. At the end of the day,
he says he called me and says, "Stevie,
I got a problem." I'm like, "What's the
matter, Joe?" He said, "I didn't sell
your stock, where you would have made,
you know,
$375. You took a $375 loss." I said,
"How'd that happen?" He says, "I I
forgot to execute the order." I'm like,
"Oh my god." So, I was really
distraught. I was
But the irony
was it was Compaq Computer, CPQ. And I
became the largest trader in in the
pretty much in the world in Compaq. I
would used to do anywhere between 1 to
10% of the volume every single day in
that stock years later.
And Joe says to me, "I'll make it up."
But he never made it up to me. But it's
okay. So, but then, I learned through a
friend of mine,
uh
Steve Carvellas on the COMEX,
about consistency.
How he taught me
how you set goals for yourself every
single day. So, his goal was to make
$100 every single day from my something
and then 200, then 300, then 400, then
500. So, I said I'm out I'm out So, when
I started trading with Joe, my
philosophy was to make $100 every single
day for a week and then [clears throat]
I would stop, no matter where I was
during the day.
And then, I went to 200, then 300.
And then,
in in 11 months, I think I made about
1.8 1.9 million dollars back in 1991.
I was staggering amount of money back
then.
And kept on just doubling up, you know,
everything that Steve taught me.
And then,
I decided I was going to go trade my own
money.
And my deal was I was going to get 30%
and Joe was going to get 70.
And then, I walked in and I said, "Joe,
I just want to let you know, uh
you know, uh I started my own firm.
And um this Friday will be my last day
and I wanted to say thank you for
everything."
And he gets his checkbook out and he
says, "Stevie, you deserve it." He says,
"Let me write you your check for 30%."
So, I said to him, "Joe, can I ask you a
really big favor?"
He said, "Whatever you want." I said, "I
know we have a 30/70 deal. Could you
make it 50/50? Since I'm going beyond."
He said, "You know what, Stevie? You
deserve it." He wrote me a big check for
about 900 grand.
I was shaking when I got the
Wow.
And I said, "Joe, can I ask you one more
favor?" He goes, "Really? One more
favor?" I says, "Yeah." I said, "What is
it?" I said, "Can I take the chair I was
sitting in?"
So, I carried the chair to the elevator
all the way down and it was just really
just an amazing He was amazing guy.
And then, I started trading my own money
and I just got into a groove. Um
Some days I was trading a million, some
days up to 5 million shares in a day.
And I just was like I was doing
high-frequency trading before
high-frequency trading came
came out.
So, did you
did you learn a lot of this from I mean,
why don't we rewind back to your to your
dad and and that era of watching him as
a trader on the American
um Stock Exchange? You know, what was it
like to watch him as a trader? And what
what were some of the lessons learned
early in that time from him?
Well, I watched my father with My father
had significant work ethic and I learned
that rather quickly that this game, you
really can't slack off. So, my dad was
more of an executing broker for the
member firm.
But he taught me so many things. My
father said to me,
um "I can't really teach you because,
you know, I don't want to ever have a
ruin our relationship." So, he
introduced me to a friend and every
single day I would
go see Frank and Frank would start
teaching me.
>> [snorts]
>> And um
and then, basically, I don't know. I got
to tell you, it just started like
clicking and
then I decided, you know, when I went to
the big board, then I went upstairs to
trade and I just started, you know,
always my first So, there was two
influential people Many influential
people in my life. Um but I remember
[snorts] 2:00 in the morning, I was out
when I my friend, who later passed away
in a terrible car accident, he um said
to me, "Whenever you
trade, Stevie, remember this
uh
two things you need to remember. One,
never have a mortgage on your home.
Okay? You never want to have a mortgage
when you're trading your own capital.
And two,
you never want to um
uh borrow money in the industry." I
said, "Got it." And um so, I when I
bought my home, I bought it for cash.
And then, my other friend said to me,
"You always And this is I think this is
where
it really clicked." And he said to me,
"You can never stay stagnant. You always
have to be 10 steps ahead of everybody
else." So,
when I went [clears throat] upstairs to
trade and
I had my own firm called Tiger
Securities.
Um, I was trading, you know, my money
but which was, you know, back then only
two to one margin, right? And so, I was
always on the cusp of violating margin
cuz I was trading so big. And then
I said this I said let me sell my firm
because then I had to take all these
exams. I said I'm not doing that. And
then I went into um
another broker dealer
um
that I put significant amount in and
then but that wasn't good enough. So,
then
because of my relationship with my
father with Peter Kellogg and Spear
Leeds and Izzy Englander and and Steve
Tobias and all the guys that worked on
the floor
um
I was given a billion-dollar line of
credit. I was the only person in the
United States to have a get a
billion-dollar line of credit.
Which helped me, you know, obviously not
violate Reg T.
And I never ever put the firm in
jeopardy. There was a couple times I was
like 999
million 998
you know, thousand I mean I I came
within thousands of going over the
billion
uh intraday. And so,
>> [snorts]
>> you know, but I respected Peter and I
never put him in harm and my name my
name never came up in a risk meeting.
And I just was just plowing away every
day. I never I knew I would I had I had
a feeling I was up on the day. But I was
trading so much
that my clerk would sometimes stay till
like 6:00 at night to recap. I mean,
when you're doing like, you know, Philip
Morris does, you know,
if Philip Morris does uh you know, 30
million shares in a day, I'm doing, you
know, 1.5 or 3 million shares
through the electronic system and
executing orders on the floor. You had
the recap and there's like eight
different price movements, you know,
Ernie had the recap. So, and and I and
then I was the largest um
uh trader in a derivative called a
bullet. You remember those days?
The bullet trades? Uh
tell me. Elaborate on it. I mean, you
and you said you were the number one
trader in the world at one time
essentially.
>> I was the number one day day
my my clearing firm told me I was the
number one day trader in in the world at
a 97.4%
hit ratio.
>> You were essentially a market maker,
were you, with the volume you were? I
was I mean, I traded 90 to 100 names. I
would have at any given time anywhere
between 30 to 50 positions. I I'm
talking positions on
and
um
but I you know, I I was, you know, very
I was it was just a gift I was given
and, you know, I I I just loved it so
much like it was my life and still is
and then
when the markets went to decimalization
um
there was lack of transparency in the
market, no depth of the market. And I
fought against that.
Um and then I said out with this, I'm
going to go build software.
And the software
I thought was going to take me one year
of my life
took me 10.
And then I forward tested it.
And I literally can tell you based upon
what I built
and now I'm working with quant guys to
get a really super automate, you know,
really really uh high advanced Yeah, I
forgot. So, the SK trading that you have
today, I mean, take us back to the
origins of that. What was the idea that
you conceived originally that okay,
there's there's something here. Like
there's something here to the market
where we can develop a technology that
kind of forecast the future.
So, that's a great question. Um so, many
years ago, I was intrigued I don't watch
any television.
I literally don't. I watch sports. I
mean, when I say I don't watch any
documentaries, I don't watch TV. I watch
sports. Like March Madness is my
favorite time of the year.
Um [snorts]
and and so, one day I was home
and I end up I turned the TV on
and uh
there was a TV show, a financial show,
and they were saying how all day traders
pretty much fail.
And that, you know,
uh it's impossible that they they should
give their money to professionals money
managers and and I went completely
crazy. I'm like, this this is BS.
Um and I'm going to teach people
that if I'm doing this and I'm
successful, I want to teach them. And I
have a methodology and I have
technology.
Right? So, I started doing this
and my membership is through the roof.
And people I I stream in over 100
countries around the world and I'm
trading real capital and I'm trading and
I'm teaching them. I can't give
investment advice, but I'm teaching them
the patterns like today, for example, we
got a big buy signal on the 30-minute
time frame on on the market on the Qs,
the spiders, the diamonds and
and I when I got this beautiful buy
signal
around [snorts] and I said it was going
to happen 11:00 between 2:00 and 3:00
and we got it exactly at 3:00. The S&Ps
ran 30, the Nasdaq ran 100 140. And so,
what I developed was something that I
wanted to and I thought it was going to
take me one year of my life. It was
close to 10 and about close to $2
million of my own money to shoo
develop it.
And um and I forward tested it. And when
I forward tested it, I worked with some
of the biggest traders in the world. As
I'm getting my signals and trading, I'm
trading with them and I'm giving them
ideas and they were just killing it.
So, I said to myself you know,
um but I'll take a step back before
that. So, American International Group
uh AIG
uh contacted me in 2002.
And I went to Stanford, Connecticut and
they wanted me to run a
staggering amount of money.
And I turned the money down.
They said, "What are you crazy?"
I says, "No, I'm not No." They said,
"Why? You you trade a billion a day. We
mean, we see your track record. It's
It's unbelievable."
And I said
"I don't feel um
ready to do this type of trading, the
long short. I want to build technology.
Give me a year." They said, "Okay, you
got one year, but we want you. You
really want to take a year?" I said,
"Yeah, a year of my own money to develop
something."
Well, I called them back a year later
and said
"I'm not ready. I don't want to do a job
half-assed for you."
>> Yeah. Yeah. And um and I worked with
some of the biggest guys in the world uh
even throughout the whole thing and just
consulting and helping them and
whatever. But then
I um
I decided
to go forward and it took me
nine more years to develop this. Now,
the one thing I can tell you
is that, you know, [clears throat] price
leads and indicators lag.
And so, but the indicators when I have
them the way I have them, they tell a
story. All my strategies are based upon
divergences.
Um so, and I use multiple time frames.
So, three time frames, five conditions
and 10 strategies.
And these patterns repeat themselves.
It's crazy.
You mentioned about certain times of the
day. I know exactly when certain times
of day when something's going to happen.
Boom. I know exactly, okay, at this time
this is going to happen. Boom. Just like
today, I said between 2:00 and 3:00, the
30-minute time frame is going to set up.
Get ready to buy them. So, when the S&Ps
were trading at 95, 94, 93, we backed up
the truck, spiders, the Qs, the
diamonds, the whole world, Micron, the
whole world, everything lined up.
And then boom, Nasdaq. Nasdaq ran
>> What were you trying to solve originally
there when developing your systems?
Because, you know, it's a lot of traders
they base
originally when they start trading, they
base a lot off of feel
instead of trying to build that process.
And I've actually heard you say as well
that you there was a period of time for
10 years you didn't even have a losing
month or year. And is that when you had
developed these systems and you were not
basing your trades after on feel
anymore. You were basing your decisions
now on the process.
Well, I I created a bunch of strategies
during that 10 year and um
like, you know, I was one of the largest
bullet traders in the world um if not
the biggest. Um which a derivative was
where it was a derivative where I could
go up on what's called a married put,
make me net long and I could sell on
back in those days destabilizing tick
short and things [clears throat] like
that that the people don't understand
today. But um
yeah, for those 10 years, nearly 10
years, I didn't have a losing month or a
losing year.
And and I mean, I attribute that to
Oh my god, I was talk
I was black I'm telling you I was given
a gift. I and I that's why I'm a humble
man. I I'm very humble even
>> [clears throat]
>> you know, four decades later for the for
what I was able to accomplish and
achieve and the people I've met along
the way and the track record I had. I
mean, you're talking sometimes I was 10%
of the volume in some of the names.
In in in some of the biggest names on
the board. Um so, if compact at 30
million or 20 million, I was two two to
three million of that, you know?
Um, what AT&T telephone or
Oh.
So many other names, Walmart,
General Motors and Ford. Um, and there
were times I moved markets. I actually
saw one time I went up on a 10 lottery
puts and I saw 50,000 all all 10 trades
go
on the tape. They printed them and, you
know, I I called Susquehanna up and I
said, "You want my business?" I said,
They said, "Yeah." I said, "Well, you
you put all my trades up at the end of
the day I sold sales because they all
see me coming.
And, um, I was so big,
I had to change my acronyms constantly.
I mean, I had to
It was It was crazy, you know? Um,
but, um,
yeah, those days are different now and
so I had to adapt when the decimals
came. And and so I decided to build
technology and I was very fortunate.
And,
um,
I'm using it now and I and I'm building
now with, um,
>> [clears throat]
>> I'm working with some top quant guys to
have it really, um, automated and the
returns we're seeing are completely
insane.
>> Incredible. Wow, that's incredible to
hear. So, I mean, you have Stephen, 43
years in the market and passionate more
now than ever. I'm curious, like, what's
the biggest evolution you've seen over
those 43 years? And for example, like,
floor trading back then versus modern
trading today, what what are some key
differences there that a lot of traders
today don't understand?
I think the speed the speed of the game
has changed now versus then.
It was more of a tame market because of
the depth of the market, you know,
sometimes you could go into Ford, the
market be 45 bid and an eight, you know,
300 by 200, you know,
um, it was a lot quieter. Not
[clears throat] I mean, if the Dow moved
25 points back then, you know, now
they're moving what, 150 handles like
today on the S&P. So, I think the speed
has changed, but also what has evolved
is like you see like Robinhood has 11
million traders, 11 million customers.
You never really realized the growth
potential of the retail trader in the
game, right? So, I think the two things
that I can see that really have
surprised me is one,
the speed of the market,
um, and with the algorithms. I mean, you
know, you can see the S&P's go
up [snorts] 50, down 20 like that, all
within eight seconds, you know? So, the
speed of the market and I think I'm
also, uh, shocked at the ability
to see the markets,
uh,
really resonate with so many retail
traders.
Now, I'm getting so many people from
around the world, "Please teach me.
Please teach me." I'm getting people now
asking me to teach them to day trade
or, uh, and learn my methodologies,
whether it's in forex, whether it's in
index futures, commodity futures,
underlying ETFs or even crypto, um,
because they're worried about, like, is
their job going to be safe in three
years with AI?
And they want to learn and for me the
ability to trade markets.
Yeah, I've watched a I've watched a lot
a lot of your live streams and you have
a great user engagement. There's a huge
community there and here's the one thing
I found fascinating. You're calling
everyone out by name in chat. You're
giving everybody your phone number.
You're you're making yourself available
to everybody. No No one does that. What
Why do you Why do you do that? And
>> Because I want Yeah, because I think
that my father always taught me to be
humble and, um,
>> [clears throat]
>> my daughter is
God willing once will be a doctor one
day and I told her I said, "Allie, if
I'm here or not here, I want you to
always remember what I'm teaching you. I
want you to treat people with kindness."
Yeah. And she is. And I want you to
always give out your phone number to any
patient that needs it to make them feel
comfortable and secure,
>> Wow. right? So, for me, I get phone
calls all the time and I I've never
missed the phone call. I've always
returned people or I called them. I just
tell them don't write me a thesis. And I
just got a I just got someone from
Canada just now wrote me, had to be
probably 900 words. So, I'm just going
to call the person, you know, and talk
to them. And, uh, but I I find it
because I think that
people, um,
>> [clears throat]
>> uh, people look at this game and they
see a lot of shysters. They see a lot of
people who are just, you know, one guy
got busted because he he rented a bunch
of Lamborghinis and he claimed he owned
them. I I Somebody told me. Um, and and
this game to me is pure.
You know, I work with some of the best
biggest guys in the world, right? And
this game to me is pure. So, I want to
be able
to mentor people, to teach them, to let
to help change their lives. And if they
have my phone number, and that gives
them great, you know, security knowing
that, "Hey, I can pick up the phone and
call this guy or text this guy. Can you
call me?" I wake up in the morning and
I'll probably get anywhere between five
and 30 "Please call me." and I call
everybody back before the opening. Wow.
Are you ready to get serious about
options trading? Then join tastytrade,
Investopedia's best platform for options
trading 2026. Stocks, options, futures,
and more. tastytrade has everything you
trade all in one platform. Get low
commissions including a $10 cap per leg
on options trades so you can keep more
of what you earn. tastytrade is packed
with advanced charting tools,
backtesting, a pre-built strategy
selector, and more features to help you
trade smarter. Manage your positions
with speed and precision using active
trader mode, one-click trading, and
smart order tracking. Plus, tastytrade's
stellar trade desk team offers live
support during trading hours if you need
it. Join tastytrade today and earn a
double commission rebate up to $3,000
total on your stock and ETF option
trades for 30 days. Visit
tastytrade.com/chat
for more info. All applicable
regulatory, exchange, and clearing fees
still apply. Options involve risk and
are not suitable for all investors.
Learn more about tastytrade promo terms
and conditions at tastytrade.com/double.
Offer expires May 31st, 2026. tastytrade
Incorporated is a registered
broker-dealer and member of FINRA, NFA,
and SIPC.
Yeah. Yeah, I was going to ask you,
Stephen, like, what's your what's your
day-to-day look like from with the time
you wake up until post market? I know
you're incredibly incredibly busy. I
don't know if you get any sleep. I mean,
what does that day look like?
Apparently, it starts with
calling everybody.
No, it's like at
4:00 I get up around 4:00 every morning,
4:30. I make a cup of coffee. I'll take
the dog out for a walk.
>> [snorts]
>> I come back, you know, I'll I'll shower.
Um, I'll call the people in Europe when
I see a, you know, a a number from my
WhatsApp or European number, I call them
first back. Um, then I'll, you know,
it's too a little bit too early to call
the people here in the United States.
Um, and then I'll, um,
I may do a lesson with someone in
Singapore or in another part of the
world, uh, Indonesia, Australia. I'll do
like a like, you know, 6:00 to 7:00
lesson. Then I'll, um,
I'll make the the New York calls or the
the US calls per se.
And then about 8:30 then I get ready. I
do my live stream from 8:30 to 4:00. Um,
then I do my podcast, my own podcast
called The Bull, The Bear, and The Ugly
on my SK Trading YouTube. It's about 10
to 15 minutes long. And then, um, I'll
go eat. Maybe I'll see my kids cuz
they're close by me. And then I come
back and I do the Asia session
for, uh, a a prop firm called My Funded
Futures and, um, I'm I love it. I mean,
we get a, you know, a big audience and,
you know, we're looking at the markets
in silver, gold, oil, index, Nasdaq, and
S&P.
And, uh, I taught them to
I actually 10 months ago when I started
this I said, "We're going to do the gold
markets." I'm like, "What are you,
crazy? Who trades gold and silver?"
Well, guess what? Now you can't keep
them away from it, okay?
>> [laughter]
>> And, uh, Yeah. And so, basically, those
two hours every And then 10:00 um,
I'll get probably anywhere from five to
50 people that want, you know, to talk
to me and I'll talk to them at 11:00 I
shut my phone off, boom, and then, um, I
think I'll take a shower. I go to bed
and I get up and do the whole thing all
over again.
So, that's You're operating on a few
hours of sleep.
>> the end of guys that funny look stupid,
trust me.
You love your life so much, sleep is
just it just Yeah, because You didn't
have to sleep, it sounds like. Uh, you
know what it is? So, I really love it. I
love it when people at the end of the
day text me their P&L's, text me what
they've done, passing an evaluation. Uh,
"SK, thank you, you know, you've changed
my life." Uh, guy last year I I I have
cards from people that are mailed to me
all around the world. Um, and it gives
me a great joy when I know that, um,
this is one of the hardest industries or
businesses in the world. And if I could
teach them and if we could change their
lives and I try to make trading fun. I
have a soundboard. I make, you know, I
have I came up with the word kabooshed.
I'm in the urban dictionary with that,
you know.
>> [laughter]
>> Um
I found out yeah.
And so like, you know, I um
I love explaining patterns like today
for example we caught this great long
off the 30 minute and then at the end of
the day we caught a phenomenal short in
gold and it dropped like 20 points, you
know. And so, you know, this this is um
this is I love this though. This is your
passion and and the passion So here's
the question. I mean your passion has
sustained for 43 years. That's that's
longevity and you know in this business
longevity
I mean it's not a lot of traders
[clears throat] fall by the wayside over
the years. So what do you think has
sustained you over 43 years?
I think um
well I hate to lose, right?
And I'm very competitive.
And um I find myself when I
come across someone new male or female
that I'm able
to hear them hear their troubles
and I love fixing it. I love helping
them.
And I don't know what it is,
but this passion
is like okay, let's go. Let's do it. I'm
getting them off I'm going to fix you.
You're going to listen to me. You're
going to learn from me. You're going to
um
follow and understand and you're going
to ask questions along the way.
Um and then when they become like
somebody [clears throat] said to me, I
want to send you a gift. I'm like, no
the gift that you sent me is your
success. You know, I don't need
anything. I'm good. Okay?
Um guy calls me up and says, "I want to
send [clears throat] you something.
You've changed my life." I'm like, "No,
you've already given me the gift. You're
successful."
Because,
you know, but that to me is that to me
is
the passion that I have
because
you know, when you're when you have
passion like I did with the game of
baseball or
in that when it took me 10 years to
build my my my software.
Um
you know, you
you just [clears throat] have that in
you.
And now for me I think at SK Trading I
want to be able to
really um
build this in a way and I'm you know,
I'm
I'm looking right now to build what's
called a trader's cafe
up where I'm going to have people come
from all around the world um be part of
this and I'm looking for some space here
in West Palm and um
I get
it's just you know what it is? It's just
so I just you just feel alive. You just
feel alive. Yeah.
Yeah. Wow.
So you you got another 20 left in you
then huh? 30 another 43 another 43 I I I
exercise and I don't smoke. I maybe have
a couple drinks during a
month, but uh
you know,
>> [clears throat]
>> I always joke with people because
you know, I may
when I was 28 years old and I was with
this guy and he says, "You know, Stevie
you don't drink." I go, "Yeah, I got
teetotaler award in high school. I don't
drink." He said, "Why?" I said, "Because
I came from nothing and I don't want to
waste a day
and I don't want to have a hangover or
something." He says, "Okay, do me a
favor.
Gentleman's bet." I said, "Okay, what's
the gentleman's bet?"
And he goes, "I'm going to get you a
Johnny Walker Black and club soda." And
he says, "You're going to drink it."
And I go, "No, I'm not. I'm not going to
drink it." He says, "No, no, no, you're
going to drink it.
You have [snorts] a drink with me
and if you have a hangover tomorrow, I'm
going to give you $10,000 cash."
I said, "Really?" He goes, "Yeah, but
you got [clears throat] to be honest." I
said, "Okay." So he orders me a drink. I
go, "Hmm, this is pretty good, right?
Not bad. My first drink in
whatever
and I think one of my first drinks I've
ever had in my life obviously.
So the next day I come in
and he walks over to me. He goes,
"I got $10,000 in my pocket. Tell me the
guy is not honest truth." I said, "I
have no hangover." And he says, "Thank
you for being honest." He said, "See,
that drink doesn't give you a hangover."
I said, "Okay." So
so often I have a Johnny Walker and and
so I I I was I have my my community is
so amazing. The jokes and the
you snap your fingers and it's 6 and 1/2
hours gone. You know,
it's it's incredible. Yeah, yeah, it's
incredible. So what with the modern
landscape, what are your thoughts on it?
Cuz today we have a lot of you know,
prop firms. That's they've exploded.
What are your thoughts on the prop firm
space?
Well, I think the prop firms really have
a significant place because
well, there's two things. I so I was out
to dinner with Terry Duffy the head of
the CME
the CEO many years ago
on his birthday. We went I was in
Chicago. We had dinner at Rosebuds and
and he was telling me how he was so
excited about the micros coming out and
>> [clears throat]
>> and his board wanted to go to Bitcoin
futures first and then eventually
because
the micros were backseat and then he
finally came out. So that was a big game
changer, but then the prop firms came
out.
And these prop firms basically if it
wasn't for the micros and if it wasn't
for the prop firms, you would have
probably north of couple million people
not trading,
right? That's a lot. Well learning to
trade
cuz a lot of people don't have the money
to commit to put in the and plus if they
did, these margins are like through the
roof. Look what they did to silver and
gold and during the crazy nonsense the
last three or four months. So these prop
firms have strict rules and I get it,
you know, the evaluations are hard to
pass, but the people who come to me in
my group,
I
have a methodology methodology not only
to trading, but the methodology to to
pass these things,
right?
>> [clears throat]
>> I'm not an affiliate.
So I don't go give out to call SK and
then I get a check for 100 grand every
month. No, no, no, I don't do that.
My goal is to teach you to trade whether
you have one account or five accounts.
Now I have like I said, I have my own
methodology in trading which I teach
and then
>> [clears throat]
>> and
on top of it I'm doing my live trading
and then you have
the people who want to learn how to
trade
>> [cough]
>> prop accounts.
Now I mean the space has gotten what?
[clears throat] Just about 25 or 35 now
to a degree,
but in the end they're they're needed.
They're warranted. And you know, like
today for example like seven or eight
guys new people that just signed up with
me about a week ago all just flashed
their certificates today.
Stevie, thank you. I just passed on I
just passed on my funded futures. I just
passed on this one. I passed on this
one. Thank you. I on that last trade on
the long. I just passed the eval. I
said, "Okay, now you got to be
consistent. Now you passed and now we
just got to chip away every day."
So it's good because so many people that
I have
are making north of six figures.
Incredible.
It's It really is.
Yeah, so I mean in this in the future
space here. I mean what what are some
patterns that you see in traders who
succeed versus fail with these
evaluations and then moving forward into
the funded?
So what breaks my heart Kevin
is when I get a phone call from someone
who's struggling and says, "I spent, you
know,
four to five thousand. I bought, you
know, 20, 30, 40 evaluations." One
person called me up one time. I swear
you're not. Said they spent
I think 18,000
and [clears throat]
they they failed 100 evals.
So
I think [clears throat] what people try
to do is remember one of my five
keywords is patience, right?
And
>> [clears throat]
>> and so
I think what people try to do is they
rush the process
and they don't have a mentor that
teaches them. They don't know what
they're doing, right?
I I break it down for people and I teach
them well and I'm telling you holy cow.
It's like boot camp times 10.
And but guess what?
I change them. I teach them. I educate
them. I I'm helping them and and my
community helps everybody.
>> [snorts]
>> And
you know, it goes back to that
when I saw
the person say, "Oh, nobody all day
traders fail. They should just put their
money with money money managers." I'm
like, "What are they crazy?"
Well, they they're talking to me now,
you know, and I said,
"But these prop firms,
you know, have strict rules and you have
to learn the rules and I do know the
rules for most of them, but I think
what's really important
why people fail cuz they don't have
a game plan. You can't be
the head coach of the Dallas Cowboys
tell all your guys take the week off and
then get ready to play on Sunday and
they'll look at you okay, what's the
game what's the plays? What's the what's
the game plan, right? And and that's
what most people fail.
And you you
you can see in the Discord even at night
SK, because of you, I I made 3,500
today. I did this. I did that. Boom,
boom, boom, boom, boom. One after the
other. And it's so rewarding. And I tell
people
you have to have a methodology. You have
to learn a skill.
And you know, after what I've been
through and
seen almost every market that you can
think of,
you have to be able to adjust and learn
how to trade certain patterns and sizing
up and scaling into a position versus
trading single lot entries.
There's a whole litany of things that I
I've completely shifted people
completely around, Kevin.
>> Yeah. And I mean, you've done much of
that with your community. And I was
going to ask you, how [clears throat]
important do you think it is to be in a
community like yours?
Oh, I
>> To be in a community in general. Yeah.
Yeah, I think that's a really good
question because most people would lose
their minds if they traded by
themselves.
Right?
>> Yeah. I think they need a community.
They My There's no one in my community
who would ever If somebody asked like a
really like, what what is cover me? You
know, like I would say, okay, SP just
dropped, you know, eight here. I'd be
looking to cover shorts and lowering
your stop. So, he said, what does cover
mean? Nobody ridiculed that person.
Nobody says, you know, this thing this
ain't for you. You know, what it you
know,
five or eight or 20 people explained
what cover meant before I even did. You
know, I think it builds
I it builds unity. It builds trust. It
builds an enormous bond
that and they know how much I care for
them all. You know, and how much that I
want them to succeed.
I'm not interested in the guy to come to
me and in two days leave.
And he goes he didn't make his Ferrari
payment, right? Uh, and
I say to that person,
did you go to college? Oh, yeah, I went
to Arizona State. So, you went 4 years?
That's correct. Did you get your
certificate and made [snorts]
degree in 2 days?
You know,
so he goes, no. I go, okay. So, you're
not the person that I really want. You
think you're going to learn what I know
in 44 years in 2 days? You're crazy.
It takes time. Everybody is different.
Some people get this in 10 days. Some
people take 10 months. Depending on how
much time you give me and and the the
bandwidth that you have. But, it's
really the beyond that you, Kevin.
I break it down really rather simple.
I really do.
And if you just apply it instead of
being lazy, you will succeed at this.
To some degree. To some degree, correct?
Yeah.
So, Stephen, after after 43 years doing
this, what does success in trading for
you look like now? What does it mean to
you now?
I'm just a really simple guy. I just
want to go home at the end of the day
knowing that I'm in the green, that I
did right by people, that people
that people [clears throat] have done
well during the day, that [snorts] I can
help them through tough volatile
markets, I can explain
different asset classes,
um,
and um,
success to me is just knowing that
I'm [clears throat] always there for
them.
Um, Man.
>> You know, I'm scared to look at my phone
now because I'll probably have about 80
messages, you know. You have such a
heart for traders. Is what I'm hearing.
Such a heart. I mean, is that what
you're most proud of?
Yeah, you know, the thing is I care for
them and like some of them I've met,
some of them I haven't met.
You know, I have a Pac-Man. I have a
Hitman. I have an Iceman. You know, I I
I love the names. And I feel like I've
known these people for 30 years and they
know I have their back, you know. And
um, you know, so many people knew,
um,
and [clears throat] I love, you know,
women traders because I feel like women
traders are the best traders. I really
do. I mean, they they just they get it
and boom, they're off to the races and,
you know, and I'll say, you know,
Amy
>> Guys traders are caboose. Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> They are
they are uh The women [snorts] get it.
What is it? You think it's uh Oh, no.
They
very astute. Um, they ask a lot of
questions. I feel like a lot of guys
don't want to And I tell them you got to
be proactive. You can't I'm not a mind
reader. You got to be You got to be
proactive. You can't
You can't
um,
I I can't read your mind. And women are
like, hey Steve, can you explain that
explain that pattern to me? What Okay,
so this and this happened. What's the
next sequence of events, you know? And
I'll tell them this is what we're going
to look for.
This is the pullback we're looking for
or etc. This is the push up we're
looking for to get short.
So, um,
yeah, I mean, you know, to each their
own, but you know, like I said, I have
I [snorts] have people who are
experienced traders. I have people who
have been around I just talked to a guy
today from Chicago. He's from the days
of the of the of the Board of Trade pits
and
he needs some help understanding some of
these markets and
from upstairs level versus being on the
floor.
Many, many years ago.
He just wants to get fine-tuned on
certain things. So, but
>> [clears throat]
>> I come across so many different people.
I think that's also excites me.
Excites me that I'm talking to someone
from France or from Italy or from
Austria or from Germany or from
Singapore uh, Australia and how they
you know, and then you know, they say,
oh, I can't believe you I'm talking to
you. I'm like, no, no, no, cut that out.
No, no, no, no, no. Don't don't do that.
I don't like that. I'm here just like
I'm just like you, you know.
But, I I want people to
really succeed. And I think that to me
is the really the most important aspect
of why I wake up every single morning
and do this. I don't really need to do
this. I have a gigantic pool of capital.
I could just trade all day long.
Right? But, I do it while I'm doing this
because
it really I've I've seen the lives of
change from a single mother raising her
child.
Um,
>> [clears throat]
>> I was on the phone today with a
a single father raising his son and how
much I've helped them, you know? And I
never knew these people before. I never
met met them, but
>> [clears throat]
>> I get close to them during the day. Like
I know like I know them for for a long
period of time.
So, what do you have to say to the
trader? I mean, for those that
have watched your videos, I mean, they
know you you're calling signals all day.
You have north of 44 screens up making
calls all day long.
And even though traders, they know what
to do,
still a lot of traders fail. And why do
you think Where where is that gap? What
what is that gap? Can you bridge it?
Yeah, I mean, a lot of times that yeah,
so there could be a combination of
things. It could be emotion. It could be
lack of skill. It could be lack of
learning. It could be like they are just
like one trader came to me a couple
weeks ago and said I blew an eval. I go,
how did you do that? He goes, well, the
market dropped and I didn't have a stop
order. And I'm like, okay, so can I ask
you a question? I said, do you have
children? He goes, yeah. I said, okay,
great. Do you ever go with your children
in a car somewhere? He goes, yes, sir. I
said, could you ever
hit the brake? He said, yes. I go, okay,
now imagine driving your kids somewhere
without having a brake in the car. Okay?
You're not brake. I said, is that common
sense? He says, oh, I see your point.
So, I think that a lot of people don't
understand this is a rule-based game.
Right? Yeah. And [snorts] and I think
that there you have to look at yourself
like an athlete.
This game this trading requires you to
be like an athlete
to take care of your body, to take care
of your mind, to be you know, to work
out, to eat right, to
get [clears throat] prepared. Um, you
know,
to get your mind completely When I walk
through that door every single day, I'm
a complete different person than when I
walk I'm another person outside that
door. You have to be able to know
>> [clears throat]
>> the rules of discipline, the rules of
preservation of capital, the um,
the art of constant repetition, right?
And I think that what most people a lot
of people fail and I and I really
instill this over and over
with people to the point where they're
going to be sick they get sick of my
voice is because I say the same thing
over and over
over and over again. Just like the
patterns repeat over and over again. I
tell the people when I'm slow, this is
what I say. You got to This is what I
would do. This is the mindset. You got
to look at the bigger time frames. You
got to have the mindset. You can't trade
into
uh, economic calendar news. You wait
till the dust settles. You got to
There's so many rules, right? But,
they're not hard. It's just that most
people
>> [clears throat]
>> just are become lazy and but I have to
say that
the people that I that come to me, you
know, [clears throat] they are, you
know, Gen Zs. They're beginners and
there are people who have traded. There
are like this so so many different
types.
But, I think [clears throat] what people
need to focus on is that this is
achievable.
Okay? And that this can really make a
significant difference in your life.
Um
And uh
But what I'm hearing from you is that
they they just need the rules. They need
the guardrails cuz a lot of traders do
come in, like you're saying, and
thinking there's so much freedom in
this.
And rules are not the forefront of their
mind. What's forefront is what? Profits,
right? They they want to focus on the
profits rather than focusing on your
five keys, and then money being a
byproduct of following your five keys to
success.
Yeah, it's like I said, you know, the
five rules that I have, more or less,
are just like a stepping stone. And then
I I start teaching them how Like I tell
everybody, like I know I know this may
sound stupid, I tell people
you're no different than a doctor.
They said, "What do you mean?" I said,
"Well, you know, if I go to a doctor and
I have to have an X-ray, it gets sent
out, or an MRI, or a CAT scan, you know,
a technician and somewhere in the
Midwest will read it, send it back, and
then the doctor tells me what the report
is, right? So, a doctor will look at an
X-ray [snorts] and say, "Okay, Mr.
Kalejian, you have a a broken wrist."
Okay? I'm like, "Great. Okay, wonderful.
I got to get put my hand in the in a
cast." Well, I try to train people to
understand that a chart is no different
than an X-ray or an image that you have
to interpret, right? So, I kind of make
a joke out of them. I'm like, like we're
all doctors, you know, because we're
looking at a chart, we're looking at
things, and you're determining how to
read a divergence pattern, how to see a
correlation [clears throat] study
between the continuous contract and the
underlying ETF. Um and God gave you
eyes. So, I this is exactly what we do
next, and this is how we do it, and this
is why we're looking to take the
position on. And so,
I think, like I said, that this all is a
cumulative
uh sphere of learning and approach
and mindset. And I don't And I'm not
saying this cuz I got 44, almost 44
years in the game.
If someone really applies themselves,
um this is so This is such an amazing
industry.
And to be
to conquer
um
the ability to have uh financial
freedom.
Yeah.
>> To be able to
um I have a person [clears throat] who
wakes up every morning, trades the first
two hours, goes to work, his wife goes
to work, comes home, trades the night
session, and he said,
"My I'm I'm the happiest guy in the
world, right?"
>> Yeah.
So,
Incredible. I mean, it It sounds from
from start to finish here, we we can
circle back around to I mean, it's the
competition, Steven. You're You're very
competitive in nature. Your story
started with sports, and even trading,
you're highly competitive, not just
against the other people, but with
yourself, it sounds like. And I wanted
to ask you as well, cuz your story also
starts with your father, Jack Kalejian.
If if he was here right now to give a
piece of advice, what what would he
share? He would say to me, my father
would say to me,
"Just be consistent every single day in
your life.
Uh as a father, uh as a brother,
uh and as a mentor,
uh and as a trader,
uh stick to the rules, um and you'll be
very successful in your life."
That's what he would tell me.
That's incredible.
It's incredible. Well, Steven, I just
want to say thank you so much. It's been
a privilege having you on and hearing
your story. I'm sure traders are going
to find tremendous value in your story.
And for those listening, be sure to
comment. Let us know your thoughts. Hit
the like button. Share it with your
friends. And then I also wanted to ask
you, Steven, where can traders find you,
follow your work, and learn more from
you for those that are listening?
Well, there's three places, actually.
Uh during the day from 8:30 to 4:00, you
can find me at sktrading.live.
Uh you can find me on my podcast, The
Bold, the Bear, and the Ugly, which is
uh on on my SK Trading YouTube. And at
night, during the Asia markets, from
Monday through Thursday, from 8:00 to
10:00,
uh with my Funded Futures YouTube or my
SK Trading YouTube. And uh the more the
merrier. That's it. That's what I say.
More the merrier. Hey, thank you so
much, Steven, again. I appreciate you. I
look forward to what the next 43 years
has in store for you.
>> Yes.
Thank you, brother. God bless you, and
God bless everybody. And thank you so
much. I'm really excited, and uh I hope
uh you know, you guys all come over, and
uh you know, uh really uh it's just the
greatest joy in my life is to really
help others. And and and um it's
something that I wake up, and the when I
meet new new people every single day,
it's just uh it's just a phenomenal
feeling. But thank you, Kevin. Thank you
so much for this opportunity.
Absolutely. You've reached the end of
this episode of Chat With Traders. But
rest assured, there are more episodes
loaded with real market insight and zero
hype on [music] the way soon. So, to
stay updated [singing] with each great
new release, subscribe to the podcast in
iTunes. And we'd love it [music] if
you'd leave a rating and review. We'll
catch you next time on Chat With
Traders.